<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE article PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.1.2//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.1.2/docbookx.dtd">
<article>
<articleinfo>
	<title>Gpe-Todo</title>
</articleinfo>
<mediaobject><imageobject><imagedata fileref="gpebanner.png" format="PNG"/></imageobject></mediaobject>
<sect1>
	<title>Accessing the application</title>
<para>
Gpe-Todo is available from the main GPE screen. To access it tap on the todo icon.
<figure>
	<title>GPE Main Screen</title>
<mediaobject><imageobject><imagedata fileref="mainscreen.png" format="PNG"/></imageobject></mediaobject>
</figure>
</para>
</sect1>
<sect1>
	<title>Icon Explanations</title>
<para>
<itemizedlist>
<listitem><mediaobject><imageobject><imagedata fileref="blankpage.png" format="PNG"/></imageobject></mediaobject><literallayout>Create a new task or category.</literallayout></listitem>
<listitem><mediaobject><imageobject><imagedata fileref="delete.png" format="PNG"/></imageobject></mediaobject><literallayout>Delete a selected task or category.</literallayout></listitem>
<listitem><mediaobject><imageobject><imagedata fileref="quit.png" format="PNG"/></imageobject></mediaobject><literallayout>Exit The Application</literallayout></listitem>
</itemizedlist>
</para>
</sect1>
<sect1>
	<title>Creating a New Item</title>
<para>
To create a new item tap on the blank page icon (See icon list above). You can than enter in your desired information:
<orderedlist>
<listitem><para>The summary is a short description of the task.</para></listitem>
<listitem><para>If the item had a due date you can tap the box next to 'Due:' and select the desired date by taping on the calendar icon and then using the arrows to find your date.</para></listitem>
<listitem><para>Below is the priority box, you can change this to low, standard, or high.</para></listitem>
<listitem><para>Next is the Status option, you can change that to Not started, In progress, Completed, or Abandoned.</para></listitem>
<listitem><para>When you tap on the categories button you can create new categories your task might fall under. This is usefull if you want to sort tasks by category in the main screen.</para></listitem>
<listitem><para>If you don't find a previous category you can use or like you can then tap on the blank page icon and enter in a new category using an input method.</para></listitem>
<listitem><para>To select a catogory tap on the box next to it, if you want to delete it tap on the category and then tap on the the trash icon (See icon list above).</para></listitem>
<listitem><para>In the Details box you can enter in a more indepth description of what you are supposed to do. </para></listitem>
<listitem><para>After you are finished tap on the Save icon at the bottom of the application.</para></listitem>
</orderedlist>
<figure>
	<title>Creating a new item</title>
<mediaobject><imageobject><imagedata fileref="newitem.png" format="PNG"/></imageobject></mediaobject>
</figure>
<figure>
	<title>Creating a new category</title>
<mediaobject><imageobject><imagedata fileref="newcategory.png" format="PNG"/></imageobject></mediaobject>
</figure>
</para>
</sect1>
<sect1>
	<title>Managing your tasks</title>
<para>
<itemizedlist>
<listitem><para>In the main screen you can view a list of the current things to do, to view items by the selected catogory simply tap on the all items button and then select the desired option.</para></listitem>
<listitem><para>When the task is completed you can tap on the box next to it and it will then become crossed out.</para></listitem>
<listitem><para>If you need to view a task in detail or change it you can simply tap on the name.</para></listitem>
<listitem><para>To delete the task permanently tap on the name and then the delete button at the bottom of the program.</para></listitem>
</itemizedlist>
<figure>
	<title>Viewing by category</title>
<mediaobject><imageobject><imagedata fileref="viewcategory.png" format="PNG"/></imageobject></mediaobject>
</figure>
</para>
</sect1>
</article>